elementskateboards.com 2012-06-08

# Privacy Policy | Element

**OUR COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY**  
Element Skateboards, Inc. ("Element") respects your privacy. We are particularly sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet and therefore we provide this Privacy Policy so you know about our online information practices and understand how we treat the information we receive about you from the Internet. 

**THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
In general, you can browse our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We are, however, able to determine your IP address. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our website, to measure the use of our website and to improve the content of our website. In short we use your IP to gather aggregate demographic information. There are a few places where we give you an opportunity to provide us your personal information. This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. When you engage in certain activities on our website, such as ordering a product, entering a contest or sweepstakes, filling out a survey, sending us feedback, requesting owners and parts manuals or registering your product online, we may ask you to provide certain information. If you choose to share any personal information with us, you will see that the amount and type of personal information we request depend on how you use our website. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), email address, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products on our website, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. 

**THE WAY WE USE INFORMATION**  
We may use your personal information for particular purposes such as processing your order or for marketing research and other marketing purposes and for providing you with the latest product and promotional information and other information that might be useful to you. We may use your personal information to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding administrative notices. We may share this information with Element affiliates, dealers or other business partners to support your customer relationship with the company. We must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for products purchased on our website; release your address information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered; and provide order information to third parties that help us provide customer service. We will not give or sell this information to any other company for its use in marketing or solicitation. 

* * *

**UPDATING AND CORRECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
You may access and correct your personal information by writing us at: 

Element Skateboards, Inc.  
121 Waterworks Way  
Suite 100  
Irvine, CA 92618 

Please include your name, address, and/or email address when you contact us.  
We encourage you to promptly update your personal information if it changes. 

**YOUR CHOICE ON COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**  
We may, from time to time, send you mailings regarding our products and services. We will send you these mailings only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers. If you do not wish to receive further information from Element you can send us an e-mail at [store@elementskateboards.com](mailto:store@elementskateboards.com) and tell us that you do not want to receive future communications. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed, however, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on our website. In addition, it may be impossible to completely delete your information without some residual information because of backups. 

We will encourage our service partners to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your personal information by our service partners is governed by the privacy policies of those service partners, and is not subject to our control. The Element website contains links to other non- Element websites. Element is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites and you should exercise your best judgment when sharing personal information on these websites. 

**OUR COMMITMENT TO SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
We want you to have continuing trust in Element and in our products and services and, so, we have put in place reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure your personal information. 

In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through our website cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party. 

* * *

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY POLICY**  
The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") requires that we inform parents and legal guardians about how we collect, use, and disclose personal information from children under 13 years of age, and that we obtain the consent of parents and guardians in order for children under 13 years of age to use certain features of our websites. Element does not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13. 

We may amend our Children's Privacy Policy at any time. We will provide parents notice by email or posting on our website of any material changes in the way we intend to collect, use, and/or share a child's personal information. We will apply material changes in our Children's Privacy Policy only in conformance with applicable law, including any applicable provisions of COPPA that require parental consent. 

By using this website you are agreeing to the terms of the Element Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify our privacy policy as business needs require. We will post such changes on our website.
